<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scroller App</string>
    <string name="heading">2020 Summer Olympics opening ceremony</string>
    <string name="subheading">Preparations</string>
    <string name="article">The Tokyo Organising Committee of the Olympic and Paralympic Games (TOCOG) gave the first report of preparations in December 2017, with the release of the \"Basic Policy\" document for the Olympic and Paralympic ceremonies.The document was based upon feedback from experts and opinions of the Japanese public and includes the foundational elements for the positioning and overall concept of the four ceremonies. The Olympic opening ceremony is to introduce the themes and concepts of the four ceremonies, including peace, coexistence, reconstruction, the future, Japan and Tokyo, the athletes and involvement.\n
        The opening and closing ceremonies have had three different directors as its chief creative director. Between July 2018 and December 2020, Mansai Nomura, an actor in traditional Japanese theater, was the chief creative director.[9][10] Normura stepped down from the role as the original ceremony team disbanded.[11] He became an advisor.
        Between December 2020 and March 2021, Hiroshi Sasaki was chief creative director, until Sasaki resigned after making a derogatory comment about Japanese comedian and fashion icon Naomi Watanabe. The reports came a month after Yoshirō Mori, president of the Tokyo 2020 Organising Committee, resigned over derogatory comments made about female members of the Committee. Since March 2021 until 22 July 2021, Kentarō Kobayashi was made chief creative director, with Takayuki Hioki, managing director of Sports Branding Japan, promoted to deputy chief ceremonies officer and executive producer.
        Marco Balich of Balich Worldwide Shows, is the Senior Adviser to the Executive Producer. Balich was involved as producer of the ceremonies of the 2006 Winter Olympics, 2014 Winter Olympics and the 2016 Summer Olympics, and has done other international ceremonies such as the 2019 Summer Universiade and the 2019 Pan American Games in Lima. In July 2019, he mentioned that his involvement will be in partnership with the Japanese advertising company Dentsu. Dentsu\'s creative director for these ceremonies, Kaoru Sugano, resigned in January 2020 over harassment claims.
    </string>
</resources>